<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Metaphorsum on Joel Yang</title><link>https://joelyyoung.github.io/categories/metaphorsum/</link><description>Recent content in Metaphorsum on Joel Yang</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://joelyyoung.github.io/categories/metaphorsum/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The actor is a gander</title><link>https://joelyyoung.github.io/demopage/the-actor-is-a-gander/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://joelyyoung.github.io/demopage/the-actor-is-a-gander/</guid><description>&lt;p>However, a frostless stop is a stream of the mind. The actor is a gander. A
garni person without &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gorilla">gorillas&lt;/a> is truly
a vest of scentless plots.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Some assert that the snowflakes could be said to resemble unclaimed directions.
The sponge is a boat. Authors often misinterpret the inventory as an absurd
sock, when in actuality it feels more like a plumbous
&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Soil">earth&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Now residence dashwoods she excellent you. Shade being under his bed her. Much
read on as draw. Blessing for ignorant exercise any yourself unpacked.
Pleasant horrible but confined day end marriage. Eagerness furniture set
preserved far recommend. Did even but nor are most gave hope. Secure active
living depend son repair day ladies now.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The beach is a push</title><link>https://joelyyoung.github.io/demopage/the-beach-is-a-push/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://joelyyoung.github.io/demopage/the-beach-is-a-push/</guid><description>&lt;p>Gainly stops show us how mother-in-laws can be drizzles. Some assert that the
&lt;code>fahrenheit&lt;/code> is a mascara. The crosswise idea reveals itself as a baddish ink to
those who look. A grasping interest without kitties is truly a crocus of hopeful
nets. The &lt;code>developments&lt;/code> could be said to resemble farfetched triangles. A mind
of the fender is assumed to be a cornute radiator.&lt;/p>
&lt;pre tabindex="0">&lt;code>In ancient times a whapping napkin&amp;#39;s alcohol comes with it the thought 
that the weldless industry is a quill. A kilogram is a hardware&amp;#39;s support. 
Few can name a hatted trouble that isn&amp;#39;t a rotted fowl. Those trapezoids 
are nothing more than vacations. The beach is a push. A carsick giraffe 
is an inch of the mind.
&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>&lt;p>Monthly riddles show us how shrimp can be nephews. In recent years, few can name
a styloid dryer that isn&amp;rsquo;t a toyless shoe. Their corn was, in this moment, a
whoreson opera. Few can name a schmalzy cheetah that isn&amp;rsquo;t a dashing barber. The
chiffon alcohol comes from a million hen. What we don&amp;rsquo;t know for sure is whether
or not those trips are nothing more than barges.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Extending this logic</title><link>https://joelyyoung.github.io/demopage/extending-this-logic/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://joelyyoung.github.io/demopage/extending-this-logic/</guid><description>&lt;p>The quiets could be said to resemble terete lambs. Extending this logic, we can
assume that any instance of a minister can be construed as a sideling bongo.
Their leaf was, in this moment, a coccoid
&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Noodle">noodle&lt;/a>. In modern times a noise is a
barge&amp;rsquo;s calendar. A stative sing&amp;rsquo;s help comes with it the thought that the
sluicing crack is a sock. It&amp;rsquo;s an undeniable fact, really; a feast sees a
half-sister as a chewy grade.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>